https://www.telonic.co.uk/terms_privacy.asp

Go!
Kikusui PCR-WE Series
Fixed Frequency Converters (50/60Hz)
Fixed Frequency Converters (400Hz)
Sale Items
COVID-19 Status: We Are Currently Still Shipping All Orders As Normal. Free UK Mainland Delivery On Orders Over £75.00.
Read More...
PRODUCTS
AC POWER SUPPLIES
Kikusui PCR-MA Series (PWM Type)
Models 9
Kikusui PCR-LE Series (Amp Type)
8 Models
Kikusui PCR-M Series (PWM Type)
9 Models
Kikusui PWR-01 SeriesDC Programmable Wide Range Power Supplies
12 Models
Kikusui PBZ SeriesHigh Speed Bi-Polar 4 Quadrant Power Supplies
9 Models
Lab-Power LAB-DC SeriesHigh Power Rack Mount DC Power Supplies
Over 100 Models
Lab-Power LAB-DCH SeriesHigh Power Rack Mount DC Power Supply
Over 150 Models
Delta Elektronika SM3300Series Bench / Rackmount DC power Supply
Voltage : 0-18V to 0-660V
Current : 0-5.5A to 0-220A
Power : 3300W
LAN, Digital I/O*, Isolated Analogue*, Master Slave*, RS232*, RS485*, RS422*, USB*
Delta Elektronika SM15K SeriesRegenerative Bi-Directional Sink / Source DC power Supplies
Voltage : 0-70V to 0-1500V
Current : 0 - +/-30A to 0 - +/-450A
Power 15kW
LAN, Digital I/O*, Isolated Analogue*, Master Slave*, RS232*, RS485*, RS422*, USB*
Delta Elektronika High Power SystemRegenerative Bi-Directional Sink / Source DC power Supplies
Voltage : 0-70V to 0-1500V
Current : 0 - +/-30A to 0 - +/-9000A
Power 15kW to 300kW
LAN, Digital I/O*, Isolated Analogue*, Master Slave*, RS232*, RS485*, RS422*, USB*
Max Duty / Slew: 10kHz - 20A/us
RS232C, LAN, USB. GPIB (Opt.)
RS232, USB, GPIB
Kikusui PLZ-U	SeriesMulti-Channel DC Load (Max 5 CH)
RS232, USB, GPIB
Delta Elektronika SM15K SeriesRegenerative Bi-Directional Sink / Source DC power Supplies
Voltage : 0-70V to 0-1500V
Current : 0 - +/-30A to 0 - +/-450A
Power 15kW
LAN, Digital I/O*, Isolated Analogue*, Master Slave*, RS232*, RS485*, RS422*, USB*
Delta Elektronika High Power SystemRegenerative Bi-Directional Sink / Source DC power Supplies
Voltage : 0-70V to 0-1500V
Current : 0 - +/-30A to 0 - +/-9000A
Power 15kW to 300kW
LAN, Digital I/O*, Isolated Analogue*, Master Slave*, RS232*, RS485*, RS422*, USB*
Rigol DL3000 SeriesHigh Voltage DC Electronic Loads
Input Voltage: 0-150V
Input Current:
0-40A/60A
Power: 200W/350W
Modes: CC, CV, CR, CP
Max Duty / Slew: 30kHz - 0.5A/us
RS232, LAN, USB. GPIB (Opt.)
Siglent SDL1000X-E SeriesHigh Voltage DC Electronic Loads
Input Voltage: 1-150V
Input Current:
0-30A
Power: 200W/300W
Modes: CC, CV, CR, CP
Max Duty / Slew: 25kHz – 2.5A/us
RS232, LAN, USB. GPIB (Opt.)
MANUFACTURERS
Premier Japanese Manufacturer of Test and Measurement Instruments and Programmable Power Supplies
Manufacturers a wide range of test equipment and systems to ensure the electrical safety and the functionality of electrical and electronic products according to international standards
China's emerging T&M leader of Digital Oscilloscopes & RF Spectrum Analysers
Professional High Power Programmable DC Power Supplies from 2.4kW to 150kW
Design and Manufacturer of very high quality Quartz Crystal Microbalances, known as QCMs
Diesel Engine Smoke Meters, Opacity Meters and Smoke Density meters: Used for measuring the opacity and smoke density of diesel engine exhaust
Manufacturer of low ripple/noise programmable dc power supplies from 6W to 300kW including regenerative bi-directional sink source units
American manufacturer of both standard and custom Frequency (RF) and Microwave components
High end producer of flux-gate precision current sensors
Micsig is a leading producer of portable battery power digital tablet oscilloscope and handheld oscilloscopes
Applied Kilovolts is a recognized leader in the design, manufacture and supply of HV power supplies for quadrupole and time-of-flight mass spectrometry
PULS is a specialist manufacturer of DIN rail power supply solutions for industrial applications. There products set standards in terms of efficiency, reliability and size
Graphtec Corp: Portable/Bench Data loggers
Aaronia: Portable Spectrum Analysers, Antennas and Signal Generators.
Design and Manufacture EMC Pre-compliance Test instruments including Near Field Probes, LISN’s, and TEM Cell’s
High Quality, precision hand-held multimeters
Siglent products includes Oscilloscopes, Spectrum Analysers, Vector Network Analysers, Function/Arbitrary Waveform Generators, Bench Power Supplies and Digital Bench Multimeters
Circuit Board mounting testing solutions for Soldering, Inspection and Hands-free measurements.
60W, 80W, 100W Soldering Irons with a variety of Tips and Heaters.
Microtest provide High Precision and Automatic measuring Instruments and Equipment.
JBC Soldering Tools provide efficient Soldering Systems with a variety of Tips
RENTAL
RENTAL AC POWER SUPPLIES
RENTAL DC POWER SUPPLIES
RENTAL ELECTRONIC LOADS
RENTAL TEST & MEASUREMENT
RENTAL SAFETY TESTERS
RENTAL RF/EMC PRODUCTS
NEWS
SERVICE
SALE
CONTACT
Products
AC Power Supplies
Kikusui PCR-MA Series (PWM Type)
Kikusui PCR-WE/WE2 Series
Kikusui PCR-LE Series (Amp Type)
Kikusui PCR-M Series (PWM Type)
DC Power Supplies
Rigol DP700 Series
Rigol DP800 Series
Kikusui PMX Series
Kikusui PWR-01 Series
Kikusui PBZ Series
Kikusui PWX Series
Lab-Power LAB-DC Series
Manufacturers
KikusuiPremier Japanese Manufacturer of Test and Measurement Instruments and Programmable Power Supplies
ETL PruftechnikManufacturers a wide range of test equipment and systems to ensure the electrical safety and the functionality of electrical and electronic products according to international standards.
RigolChina's emerging T&M leader of Digital Oscilloscopes & RF Spectrum Analysers
Lab-PowerProfessional High Power Programmable DC Power Supplies from 2.4kW to 150kW
QCMDesign and Manufacturer of very high quality Quartz Crystal Microbalances, known as QCMs
CelescoDiesel Engine Smoke Meters, Opacity Meters and Smoke Density meters: Used for measuring the opacity and smoke density of diesel engine exhaust
Delta ElektronikaManufacturer of low ripple/noise programmable dc power supplies from 6W to 300kW including regenerative bi-directional sink source units
Telonic BerkeleyAmerican manufacturer of both standard and custom Frequency (RF) and Microwave components
DanisenseHigh end producer of flux-gate precision current sensors
MicsigMicsig is a leading producer of portable battery power digital tablet oscilloscope and handheld oscilloscopes.
Applied KilovoltsApplied Kilovolts is a recognized leader in the design, manufacture and supply of HV power supplies for quadrupole and time-of-flight mass spectrometry
PULSPULS is a specialist manufacturer of DIN rail power supply solutions for industrial applications. There products set standards in terms of efficiency, reliability and size.
GraphtecGraphtec Corp: Portable/Bench Data loggers.
AaroniaPortable Spectrum Analysers, Antennas and Signal Generators
TekboxDesign and Manufacture EMC Pre-Compliance Test instruments including Near Field Probes, LISN's and TEM Cell's
BrymenHigh Quality, precision hand-held multimeters
SiglentSiglent products includes Oscilloscopes, Spectrum Analysers, Vector Network Analysers, Function/Arbitrary Waveform Generators, Bench Power Supplies and Digital Bench Multimeters
SensepeekCircuit Board mounting testing solutions for Soldering, Inspection and Hands-free measurements
Atten60W, 80W, 100W Soldering Irons with a variety of Tips and Heaters.
MicrotestMicrotest provide High Precision and Automatic measuring Instruments and Equipment.
JBCJBC Soldering Tools provide efficient Soldering Systems with a variety of Tips.
Rental
Rent AC Power Supplies
Rent DC Power Supplies
Rent Electronic Loads
Rent Test and Measurement
Rent Safety Testers
Rent RF/EMC Products
Contact
Privacy Policy
Introduction
Telonic Instruments Ltd (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle the personal information created when accessing and using our services, how we use any personal information we collect about you and why, what we do with the information and how we share it. Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal data. By providing personal data to us, you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.
Information we collect/automatic/provided- including third party
When accessing our services, we collect information to enable us to manage your account, process your orders and improve our service. Information such as name, address, phone number, email address and financial information are provided by you when completing registration.
We will also collect information such as IP addresses, domain name and referring URL, time of visit, pages visited, and any searches performed. We may also receive and share information about you with third parties we are working with such as credit referencing agencies, analytics partners, external accountants and IT support providers, couriers and manufacturers for technical purposes.
Use of Information
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
•	For the provision of services requested by you
•	To help us identify and provide information on services/products which may be of interest to you
•	To notify you about changes to our service
•	To administer and improve our site
•	To keep our site safe and secure
•	To Keep you informed of product updates.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "Contact details / access to data section” below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
We may share your Personal data with other organisations in the following ways:
In the event our assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us will be one of the transferred assets
•	If we are under a duty to disclose or share your Personal Data to comply with any legal obligation
•	Data processors who handle your data on our behalf in accordance with our instructions. Some of these processors may be based outside the UK and your information may therefore be transferred outside the UK (including, in some cases, outside Europe). Where this applies we will take steps to ensure adequate protection of your information.
Cookies
Our website uses Cookies to ensure we provide a good experience when visiting our site. Our policy regarding Cookies can be found below.
Web beacons
We may use web beacons on our Websites and in our emails. When we send emails we may track behaviour such as who opened the emails and who clicked the links. This allows us to measure the performance of our email campaigns and to help improve our features and services.
Security
We take reasonable administrative and electronic measures to protect your information. Our websites use SSL which provides encryption, authentication and message integrity. Access to stored data is password protected and access to passwords is limited. We work with our authorising banks and business partners to ensure the security of your credit card information by aligning with PCI requirements.
Passwords which enable you to access our websites must be kept confidential and not disclosed to a third party. We take our security obligations very seriously and ask that you take sensible measures to prevent your details being used in an unauthorised manner. Log out of your account fully and delete any browser history.
Policy updates
Any changes or updates to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page.
GDPR statement
We are committed to compliance with GDPR which came into effect on 25th May 2018.
Contact details/Access to data
You may contact us with any questions concerning your Personal data held by us, including any changes you wish to make and/or our Privacy Policy by emailing info@telonic.co.uk or writing to Telonic Instruments Ltd, Unit 5, The Business Centre, Molly Millar's Lane, Wokingham, Berkshire, RG41 2QZ.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.
To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.
Cookie Policy
Cookies are tiny data files placed on your computer or smart device when you visit a website. They are essential to the effective running of the website and enable you to interact with us online.
Cookies do not harm your computer or contain information, confidential or otherwise, that can help identify you to third parties.
There are different types of cookie:
Strictly necessary: Cookies that are required for the operation of our website. They allow you to move around the site, use a shopping cart or e-billing services.
Performance Cookies: These collect information about our website, the numbers and type of visitors, how they move around the site and if you experience any errors. They are used for collating data which will help improve the performance and your experience of our site.
Functionality Cookies: These are used to remember settings and choices you have made on the site. It enables us to provide a more personal service when re-visiting the site.
Targeting Cookies: Useful for determining the areas of our website of interest to you, to enable us to make our site more relevant to you each visit.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Google Chrome, Firefox, Microsoft Edge or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.
CLICK TO CALL0118 9786911
CLICK TO EMAIL
